clarkcountycourts.us 2013-05-23

# Welcome to the Clark County Courts in Las Vegas

## Privacy Statement

The Clark County Courts are committed to protecting online users’ privacy. We believe that protection  of personal privacy on the Internet is our responsibility, to assure citizen confidence,  increase participation in online activities, and support effective delivery of services. 

The purpose of our policy is to inform you about the types of information we gather when  you visit our site, how we may use that information, whether we disclose it to anyone, and  the choices you have regarding our use of, and your ability to correct, the information. The following is the privacy policy for this site.

We collect some information that is used for analysis and statistical purposes that help us  manage our Internet resources.

1\. Information that you provide us when using our interactive forms and functions. This  information may include such things as name, address, telephone number, and other personal  and business data, depending on the particular service you use. We collect only that data necessary to provide the service that you are requesting.

2\. Control of personal information. At any time, while accessing our site, any user, while  online, may decline participation in any activity that asks for information (i.e. survey, e-mail  or e-commerce). Your choice not to participate will in no way affect your ability to use any  other feature on our site. In online applications that ask for personal information, you also  are provided the option of canceling or "clearing all fields" of information and terminating the application.

3\. Use of cookies. Clark County uses cookies to store a 'tag' (identical for each user) on your  hard drive to enable automatic logon from your own computer. Clark County also adds a  unique cookie tag for each computer accessing the site. These unique tags are not linked  to individual user names, only to the computer that is used to access our site. The names  and email addresses of registered users are recorded in a database, which is used solely for  the purpose of ensuring easy logon by returning guests. If you have not enabled cookies in  your browser, these features will not work properly.

4\. Disclosure to third parties. As a governmental agency, we are governed by public records  laws. Any information that we receive through use of our site is subject to the same  provisions as information provided on paper. Otherwise, we do not share personal  identifying information with any third party without your permission. This information is not  reported or used in any manner that would reveal personally identifiable information, and will  not be released to any outside parties unless we are legally required to do so in connection  with law enforcement investigations or other legal proceedings.

If you believe that the Clark County Courts are using your personally identifiable information for a purpose  other than outlined in this privacy statement, you may contact us at input [at] co.clark.nv.us.
